<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kubeflow on AWS – Amazon SageMaker Integration</title>
    <link>https://rrrkharse.github.io/kubeflow-manifests/main/docs/amazon-sagemaker-integration/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Amazon SageMaker Integration on Kubeflow on AWS</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    
	  <atom:link href="https://rrrkharse.github.io/kubeflow-manifests/main/docs/amazon-sagemaker-integration/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
      
        
      
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: SageMaker Operators for Kubernetes (ACK)</title>
      <link>https://rrrkharse.github.io/kubeflow-manifests/main/docs/amazon-sagemaker-integration/sagemaker-operators-ack-copy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rrrkharse.github.io/kubeflow-manifests/main/docs/amazon-sagemaker-integration/sagemaker-operators-ack-copy/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/aws-controllers-k8s/sagemaker-controller&#34;&gt;SageMaker Operators for Kubernetes (ACK)&lt;/a&gt; make it easier for developers and data scientists using Kubernetes to train, tune, and deploy machine learning (ML) models using Amazon SageMaker. &lt;a href=&#34;https://aws-controllers-k8s.github.io/community/docs/community/overview/&#34;&gt;ACK&lt;/a&gt; lets you define and use AWS service resources directly from Kubernetes. With ACK, you can take advantage of AWS-managed services for your Kubernetes applications without needing to define resources outside of the cluster or run services that provide supporting capabilities like databases or message queues within the cluster.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;tutorials&#34;&gt;Tutorials&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SageMaker Operators for Kubernetes (ACK) comes installed with all &lt;a href=&#34;https://rrrkharse.github.io/kubeflow-manifests/main/docs/deployment/&#34;&gt;deployment options&lt;/a&gt; for Kubeflow on AWS.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For more in-depth guides on installing and using the new SageMaker Operator for Kubernetes, see the following tutorials:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://aws-controllers-k8s.github.io/community/docs/tutorials/sagemaker-example/&#34;&gt;Machine Learning with the ACK SageMaker Controller&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Use SageMaker Operators for Kubernetes (ACK) to manage your SageMaker resources from your Kubernetes cluster directly or from AWS-optimized &lt;a href=&#34;https://rrrkharse.github.io/kubeflow-manifests/main/docs/component-guides/notebooks/&#34;&gt;Kubeflow Notebooks&lt;/a&gt; that are built on top of &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.aws.amazon.com/deep-learning-containers/latest/devguide/what-is-dlc.html&#34;&gt;AWS Deep Learning Containers&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: SageMaker Components for Kubeflow Pipelines</title>
      <link>https://rrrkharse.github.io/kubeflow-manifests/main/docs/amazon-sagemaker-integration/sagemaker-components-for-kubeflow-pipelines/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rrrkharse.github.io/kubeflow-manifests/main/docs/amazon-sagemaker-integration/sagemaker-components-for-kubeflow-pipelines/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.aws.amazon.com/sagemaker/latest/dg/kubernetes-sagemaker-components-for-kubeflow-pipelines.html&#34;&gt;SageMaker Components for Kubeflow Pipelines&lt;/a&gt; allow you to move your data processing and training jobs from the Kubernetes cluster to SageMaker’s machine learning-optimized managed service.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These components integrate SageMaker with the portability and orchestration of Kubeflow Pipelines. Using the SageMaker components, each job in the pipeline workflow runs on SageMaker instead of the local Kubernetes cluster. The job parameters, status, logs, and outputs from SageMaker are accessible from the Kubeflow Pipelines UI.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;available-components&#34;&gt;Available components&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can create a Kubeflow Pipeline built entirely using SageMaker components, or integrate individual components into your workflow as needed. Available Amazon SageMaker components can be found in the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kubeflow/pipelines/tree/master/components/aws/sagemaker&#34;&gt;Kubeflow GitHub repository&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;tutorials&#34;&gt;Tutorials&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kubeflow on AWS includes pipeline tutorials for SageMaker components. Examples are included for the most common features that can be used to run production loads with just a few clicks. To try out the examples, deploy Kubeflow on AWS on your cluster and visit the Kubeflow Dashboard &lt;code&gt;Pipelines&lt;/code&gt; tab.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To train a classficiation model using SageMaker Components for Kubeflow Pipelines, see the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kubeflow/pipelines/tree/master/samples/contrib/aws-samples/mnist-kmeans-sagemaker&#34;&gt;MNIST classification with KMeans&lt;/a&gt; sample.&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
